[{"answer": "Bonny had people that she burned.", "docId": "120716pmt", "aSentId": 18, "question": "Who do you think killed Bonny?", "qSentId": 17}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, as you know, something very similar happened to me when I was in Congress many years ago.", "docId": "120716pmt", "aSentId": 40, "question": "What can you tell me about what happened to her?", "qSentId": 39}, {"answer": "I was with Kerry last week.", "docId": "120716pmt", "aSentId": 63, "question": "Have you managed to speak to her at all?", "qSentId": 62}, {"answer": "Well, listen, Piers, if she had been suffering from cancer, or diabetes or some other acceptable illness, she wouldn't have had any problem getting the necessary help.", "docId": "120716pmt", "aSentId": 79, "question": "Would you categorize what she went through as the kind of thing that you were talking about in terms of people who get stigmatized and sensationalized?", "qSentId": 78}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, like I said in my own circumstance, I was very fortunate.", "docId": "120716pmt", "aSentId": 99, "question": "How much of a pressure does the family feel about that kind of thing?", "qSentId": 98}, {"answer": "Well, on the face of it, you're right, they seem damaging.", "docId": "120716pmt", "aSentId": 149, "question": "What can you tell me about them?", "qSentId": 148}, {"answer": "According to the court's order, allowing for the release of her statement, I'm allowed to state the relationship.", "docId": "120716pmt", "aSentId": 160, "question": "Do you know if she is actually a relative or not?", "qSentId": 159}, {"answer": "There actually were some other events that happened in the family dynamics that we will get into if we need to.", "docId": "120716pmt", "aSentId": 176, "question": "Do you have any suspicions yourself as to why she came forward and said this now?", "qSentId": 175}, {"answer": "I think that if they could tie that to an event of George's and if, in fact, they had some other evidence supporting a suggestion of racism.", "docId": "120716pmt", "aSentId": 197, "question": "A family member alleging racism from George's family?", "qSentId": 196}, {"answer": "Well, actually, I had asked the state.", "docId": "120716pmt", "aSentId": 216, "question": "I presume after this huge dump of stuff today that feeling has been reinforced, is it?", "qSentId": 215}, {"answer": "I would disagree with you, Piers, on that comment to smear.", "docId": "120716pmt", "aSentId": 244, "question": "Is it valid?", "qSentId": 243}, {"answer": "Well, look it, Governor Romney from the very beginning has said I have the credibility to be president because I ran a business.", "docId": "120716pmt", "aSentId": 270, "question": "But why do you think it's this issue that President Obama feels so strongly is the key one?", "qSentId": 269}, {"answer": "They may.", "docId": "120716pmt", "aSentId": 296, "question": "I can accept the president who's a successful businessman?", "qSentId": 295}, {"answer": "And what that means for the next four years because that's really what they're voting for.", "docId": "120716pmt", "aSentId": 315, "question": "They judge him on his performance, don't they?", "qSentId": 314}, {"answer": "Well, there's certainly a point to be made in politics about a man running for president who takes advantage of all these presumably perfectly legal things to reduce his income tax.", "docId": "120716pmt", "aSentId": 363, "question": "What do you make though of the wider point that's being made there?", "qSentId": 362}, {"answer": "Well, it's bizarre to me.", "docId": "120716pmt", "aSentId": 400, "question": "What could it be?", "qSentId": 399}, {"answer": "I think probably the choice for vice president for Mitt Romney or any candidate is do no harm.", "docId": "120716pmt", "aSentId": 426, "question": "Is there a better one out there for him?", "qSentId": 425}, {"answer": "He'd be a sensible pick because, again, no one would notice or care.", "docId": "120716pmt", "aSentId": 431, "question": "Would he be a sensible pick?", "qSentId": 430}, {"answer": "A lot.", "docId": "120716pmt", "aSentId": 463, "question": "When you saw the interview, what went through your mind?", "qSentId": 462}, {"answer": "He did kill Bonnie.", "docId": "120716pmt", "aSentId": 471, "question": "You have absolutely no doubt that he killed Bonnie?", "qSentId": 470}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120716pmt", "aSentId": 473, "question": "Why are you so certain because he got off the criminal case?", "qSentId": 472}, {"answer": "It's not accurate.", "docId": "120716pmt", "aSentId": 486, "question": "How can you be sure that theory isn't the true one?", "qSentId": 485}, {"answer": "Well, in a nutshell, that was the motive.", "docId": "120716pmt", "aSentId": 497, "question": "What's happened to his daughter?", "qSentId": 496}, {"answer": "I have no opinion on that whatsoever.", "docId": "120716pmt", "aSentId": 521, "question": "Do you think he should be allowed to?", "qSentId": 520}, {"answer": "Yes, it is, because you opened the door, Charlie Potatoes, and you can take that to the bank.", "docId": "120716pmt", "aSentId": 531, "question": "It's not about me, is it?", "qSentId": 530}]